/*
   25 Ekim 2020 Pazar19:14:26
   User: 
   Server: LAPTOP-KA3PMMLM
   Database: WebSite
   Application: 
*/

'Aramalar' table
- Unable to modify table.  
ALTER TABLE only allows columns to be added that can contain nulls, or have a DEFAULT definition specified, or the column being added is an identity or timestamp column, or alternatively if none of the previous conditions are satisfied the table must be empty to allow addition of this column. Column 'yazari' cannot be added to non-empty table 'Aramalar' because it does not satisfy these conditions.

